## DAMJAN PJEVIĆ

damjan.pjevic@gmail.com +386 40 933 622 www.pjevic.com linkedin.com/in/damjan-pjevic/

Ambitious, reliable and open-minded individual with a great passion in tech and business. With a Bachelors in Multimedia Engineering focused in Digital Communication and a history in the computer software industry, I am in pursuit of my master's degree in business informatics at the Economics Faculty of Ljubljana. Experienced in working with the users, public speaking and working in a team and showed a history of working in the fields of programming, telecommunications, event organisation, digital media, social media and marketing.

## **EXPERIENCES**

2015 - 2016

2019	Website manager at <b>Value Add Games</b> : Updating and maintaining the website and the online shop (using WordPress, WooCommerce), producing multimedia content for different campaigns. Helped with their most successful marketing campaign.
2019	Programmer at <b>Jozef Stefan Institute</b> , Department of Intelligent Systems – Using Python and basics in auto-encoders worked on a project that builds on Sandberg's paper - Dissolving the Fermi Paradox.
2019	Took part in the <i>BEST Summer Course</i> in Wroclaw, Poland that focuses on company management and how technology and good marketing strategy can embrace its success.
2017	Selected as one of the top 20 out of 350 global teams in OnePlus Student Marketing Challenge
2016 – 2019	<b>LMMFE Video Team</b> – Broadcasting/Technical assistant at a couple of events in cooperation with RTV SLO.
2016	Regional winners in global competition OSCE Peer to Peer: Challenging Extremism by a successfully developed and pitched tool for challenging violent extremism.

- As one of the Coordinators, successfully managed the PR group for *EESTEC Competition for Android 2015* and reached out to more students than any year before.
- Took the role of Multimedia Coordinator and produced two out of three most viewed videos on their YouTube Channel.
- Took part in a week-long seminar in Istanbul, Turkey focused on Marketing and Multimedia.

2015 - 2019 Selected Class Projects:

- Extension of the Pan-European Mobile Emergency Application with extended reality (Thesis project)
- Using Android SDK created and designed a translation app for one of the Slovene dialects.
- Improved programming in Unity and WebGL with a highlighted video game project.
- Using framework Find prototyped a local indoor navigation app for our faculty.

International Student Organisation EESTEC - LC Ljubljana.

2011 - 2015 High School Debate club.

- Won third place out of 20 teams in ZainProti debate tournament 2012.
- Took part in three different YouthPass Exchanges all focused on international Peer-to-Peer communication.

## **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2019 Multimedia Engineering - Bachelor's (2015 - 2019) Average grade: 9.0

Faculty of Electrical Engineering, University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

Hochschule für Kunst Bremen, Germany (Erasmus Exchange 2017)

## **SKILLS**

Languages: Slovenian C2, English C2, Serbian B2, German B1, Russian A1.

Programming: Java, JavaScript, C#, Python, Processing, HTML, CSS, SQL, Android Studio, Unity, WordPress.

Multiple years of experience in Adobe Creative Cloud, Office Suite.

European driving license - AM, B, B1 (since 2014)